He killed a lot of robots
그는 수많은 로봇을 죽였다
Do you believe him?
그를 믿으세요?
The last person you should trust is yourself, right?
마지막으로 믿어야 할 사람은 바로 당신 자신이겠죠?
Do you remember that day in the car?
그날 차 안에서 기억나나요?
I saw you kill Anyang with my own eyes
네가 안양을 죽이는 걸 내 눈으로 봤어
It's you
당신이에요
You are still in front of An Qiu
넌 아직도 안추 앞에 있어
pretend to be a good person
좋은 사람인 척
Apparently you were the first one to push me.
나를 밀어낸 사람은 분명히 당신이 처음이었을 거예요.
You are the one with the knife in your hand
칼을 손에 쥐고 있는 사람은 바로 당신이다
You are also the one who captured the robot.
로봇을 포획한 사람도 바로 당신입니다.
You are the one who dare not admit to killing someone
감히 사람을 죽였다는 걸 인정하지 못하는 사람이군요
do you know
당신은 알고 있나요
chew
씹다
sorry
죄송합니다
I admit
나는 인정한다
i seize the chance
나는 기회를 잡는다
I gave you many opportunities
나는 너에게 많은 기회를 주었다.
Available from start to finish
처음부터 끝까지 이용 가능
they are all lying to me
그 사람들 다 나한테 거짓말을 하고 있어
You must think I'm stupid, right?
넌 내가 바보라고 생각하겠지?
I killed my brother's murderer
나는 내 동생의 살인자를 죽였습니다
as a companion
동반자로서
as a friend
친구로
sorry
죄송합니다
Shen Li
션 리
how
어떻게
I've considered three sets and want to go back.
세 세트를 고려했는데 다시 가고 싶습니다.
how so
어떻게 그렇게
After getting a new set, I get off work on time every day.
새 세트를 구입한 후에는 매일 정시에 퇴근합니다.
It's too late to be happy
행복하기엔 너무 늦었어
do your thing
네 일을 해라
OK
좋아요
What exactly will you do?
정확히 무엇을 하시겠습니까?
I just want to seek justice for An Qiu
나는 단지 An Qiu에 대한 정의를 구하고 싶을 뿐입니다.
Qingnu lied to you
칭누가 당신에게 거짓말을 했어요
Just like Luo Su lied to me back then
그때 Luo Su가 나에게 거짓말을 한 것처럼
Your brother died mysteriously
네 동생이 의문의 죽음을 맞이했어
Someone must want to help him take revenge
누군가는 그의 복수를 돕고 싶어 하는 게 틀림없어
An Qiu, don’t believe him
안 치우, 그 사람을 믿지 마세요
if you take action
당신이 조치를 취하면
I will be like him
나도 그 사람처럼 될 거야
From today on she will be your new partner
오늘부터 그녀는 당신의 새로운 파트너가 될 것입니다
Are you worried about me?
나 때문에 걱정되시나요?
you are different from them
너는 그들과 달라
It’s different from place to place, and it’s different from place to place.
장소에 따라 다르고, 장소에 따라 다릅니다.
you are important to me
당신은 나에게 중요하다
An Qiu, don’t believe him
안 치우, 그 사람을 믿지 마세요
Anyang's death won't make you take action
안양의 죽음은 당신이 행동을 취하게 만들지 않을 것입니다
it seems
것 같다
Even your initial obsession has been changed by them
너의 초기 집착마저 그들에 의해 변해버렸어
Beyond the initial obsession
처음의 집착을 넘어서
What other reason do you have to protect him like this?
그 사람을 이렇게 보호해야 할 이유가 또 뭐 있겠습니까?
This is what you think about Android
Android에 대한 여러분의 생각은 다음과 같습니다.
experimental evidence
실험적 증거
I let this happen
난 이런 일이 일어나도록 놔뒀어
Mingmou would never do this
밍무는 절대 이런 짓 안 할 거야
Yin Tianhong
인 티안훙
I found that many robots are looking at Mingming
많은 로봇들이 밍밍을 보고 있는 걸 발견했어요
I heard that even your mother participated in Mingmu's experiment.
네 엄마도 밍무의 실험에 참여했다고 들었어.
What qualifications do you have to accuse me?
당신이 나를 고발하려면 어떤 자격이 있어야 합니까?
Yin Tianhong
인 티안훙
Have you ever wondered why you are in bright eyes?
당신의 눈이 왜 밝은지 궁금한 적이 있나요?
You obviously hate Qingnuo
당신은 분명히 Qingnuo를 싫어합니다
Why do we still believe and support him?
우리는 왜 아직도 그를 믿고 지지하는가?
Don't you dare do anything to him
감히 그 사람에게 아무 짓도 하지 마
Your brother told me
네 형이 나한테 말했지
Your main concern is taking care of your family
당신의 주요 관심사는 가족을 돌보는 것입니다.
But you have become a bright-eyed experience
하지만 넌 눈이 밝은 경험이 됐어
He also wanted to protect the man who killed his brother
자신의 동생을 죽인 남자도 지키고 싶었다.
Don't they need to be punished?
그 사람들은 처벌을 받아야 하는 것 아닌가요?
Let the tragedy end
비극이 끝나기를
chew
씹다
Cheng Nu
쳉 누
Qingnu, where are you?
칭누야, 어디야?
Why are you here?
당신은 왜 여기에 있습니까?
Who was kidnapped?
누가 납치됐나요?
Is he related to Anqiu?
그는 Anqiu와 관련이 있습니까?
Nothing to do with this
이 일과는 아무 관련이 없습니다
This is what Yin Tianhong did
이것이 Yin Tianhong이 한 일입니다.
He also kidnapped An Qiu
그는 또한 안추(An Qiu)를 납치했다.
What
무엇
Then I have to call the headquarters quickly.
그럼 빨리 본사에 전화해야겠어요.
Don't say it yet
아직 말하지 마세요
We still don’t know what Yin Tianhong will do
우리는 여전히 Yin Tianhong이 무엇을 할지 모릅니다.
I am anxious
나는 불안하다
Chiyo will be in danger
치요가 위험해질 거야
You have begun to care about your partner
당신은 당신의 파트너에 대해 관심을 갖기 시작했습니다
thank you for coming
와줘서 고마워요
We are also partners, why should you be grateful?
우리도 파트너인데 왜 감사해야 합니까?
it seems
것 같다
Even your initial obsession has been changed by them
너의 초기 집착마저 그들에 의해 변해버렸어
correct
옳은
Do you know the experiment my mother did?
우리 엄마가 했던 실험을 아시나요?
Dr. Zhang’s experiments have been kept secret
장 박사의 실험은 비밀로 유지되었습니다
But I know she is cooperating with Ming
하지만 나는 그녀가 Ming과 협력하고 있다는 것을 알고 있습니다.
Laboratory funding and resources
실험실 자금 및 자원
They are all taken from inside the bright eye.
그것들은 모두 밝은 눈 내부에서 가져온 것입니다.
Enter
입력하다
you came just in time
넌 딱 맞춰 왔어
I just have something to ask you
그냥 물어볼 게 있어요
Chu Chen made a request
추첸이 요청했어요
I need to check on the monitoring of your three groups.
세 그룹의 모니터링을 확인해야 합니다.
He suspects you plan to destroy evidence
그는 당신이 증거를 인멸할 계획이라고 의심합니다
how so
어떻게 그렇게
He has hated me for a long time.
그 사람은 오랫동안 나를 미워했어요.
It must be about Xu Nianyan
Xu Nianyan에 관한 것임에 틀림 없습니다
make him feel embarrassed
그 사람을 당황하게 만들어
Why are you so nervous?
왜 그렇게 긴장해요?
Why am I nervous?
나는 왜 긴장합니까?
just me
나만
I really can't stand it
정말 못 참겠어
how old are you?
몇 살이에요?
Still noisy like a baby
아직도 아기처럼 시끄러워
Chu Chen is like this now
츄첸은 지금 이렇다
I'll take care of it
내가 처리할게
are you looking for me?
나를 찾고 있나요?
Do you know what my mom went through?
우리 엄마가 어떤 일을 겪었는지 아세요?
Why do you remember to ask this?
왜 이런 질문을 기억하시나요?
her experience
그녀의 경험
Will it replace the original obsession?
그것이 원래의 집착을 대체할 것인가?
How do you know this?
이것을 어떻게 알 수 있나요?
so it's true
그래서 그건 사실이야
correct
옳은
Bright Eyes in the Android calling sequence
Android 호출 시퀀스의 밝은 눈
Created after release
출시 후 생성됨
The dose wasn't even identified at first.
처음에는 복용량도 확인되지 않았습니다.
Judgment robot
심판 로봇
takes a long time
시간이 오래 걸린다
Thank you mom for staying with me
엄마, 나와 함께 있어줘서 고마워요
I developed an identification potion
식별 물약을 개발했어요
Significantly improve detection efficiency
탐지 효율성을 대폭 향상
However, identification potions cannot be used casually.
그러나 식별 물약은 함부로 사용할 수 없습니다.
After several miscalculations by androids,
안드로이드의 몇번의 오산 끝에,
Bright eyes in crisis
위기에도 빛나는 눈빛
your mother suggested
네 어머니가 제안하셨어
Robot focuses on his original obsession
로봇은 자신의 원래 집착에 집중합니다.
if this was their original obsession
이게 그들의 원래 집착이었다면
Be a useful person to society
사회에 유용한 사람이 되자
Maybe we can break this situation
어쩌면 우리는 이 상황을 깨뜨릴 수 있을지도 몰라
So try this thing
그러니 이것을 시도해 보세요
This is decided by the two of you.
이건 너희 둘이서 결정해.
Yes
예
But I discovered your mother's experience
하지만 난 네 엄마의 경험을 알아냈어
It brings a lot of pain to Android
Android에 많은 고통을 안겨줍니다.
I also advised her
나는 또한 그녀에게 조언했다
On the grounds that Ming no longer supports her
Ming이 더 이상 그녀를 지원하지 않는다는 이유로
tell her to stop
그녀에게 그만하라고 말해
but
하지만
She insisted on continuing
그녀는 계속할 것을 주장했다
she also told me
그 사람도 나한테 말했지
Even if Mingmou doesn't participate
밍무가 참여하지 않더라도
You'll also find others to collaborate with
또한 함께 협력할 다른 사람을 찾을 수도 있습니다.
She was angry because I didn't support her.
내가 그녀를 지지하지 않았기 때문에 그녀는 화를 냈습니다.
Then he didn't even answer my calls.
그러고는 내 전화에도 응답하지 않았다.
Why do you persist?
왜 지속합니까?
Change initial obsession
초기 집착을 바꾸다
perhaps
아마도
because of you
당신 때문에
When you enter bright eyes
빛나는 눈빛에 들어가면
Is your relationship getting worse?
관계가 점점 악화되고 있나요?
So I can understand her approach
그래서 나는 그녀의 접근 방식을 이해할 수 있습니다
as a mother
어머니로서
She hopes to cultivate a
그녀는
it can protect you
그것은 당신을 보호할 수 있습니다
Completely loyal to your Android partner
Android 파트너에게 전적으로 충실함
replace it
교체하다
stay with you
너와 함께있어
presumptuous
주제넘은
problem appear
문제가 나타남
you killed the robot
네가 로봇을 죽였어
But I didn't know he was your brother at the time
하지만 그 당시에는 그 사람이 당신의 형제인지는 몰랐어요
Who abuses robots?
누가 로봇을 학대하는가?
we never do that
우리는 절대 그런 짓 안 해
I didn't expect An Qiu to be a robot.
나는 An Qiu가 로봇이 될 것이라고는 예상하지 못했습니다.
What's even more ridiculous is that she is already at dawn.
더 우스꽝스러운 것은 그녀가 벌써 새벽에 있다는 것이다.
Now we will be in pain
이제 우리는 고통스러울 것이다
Those photos you just saw
방금 본 그 사진들
Just bright eyes
그냥 눈이 밝아
Control the life and death of all androids
모든 안드로이드의 삶과 죽음을 통제하세요
abuse of power
권력 남용
What happened to the video in Yin Tianhong’s hand?
Yin Tianhong의 손에 있던 비디오는 어떻게 되었습니까?
Obviously, the place of abuse was not in Ming.
분명히 학대의 장소는 명나라가 아니었습니다.
This is slander
이건 비방이에요
beside
옆에
What’s wrong with you
왜 그래?
I saw him this morning
오늘 아침에 그를 봤어
I didn't know he could take videos
그 사람이 동영상을 찍을 줄은 몰랐어요
minister
장관
There is a group of reporters outside
밖에는 취재진이 있다
He refuses to leave no matter what
그는 무슨 일이 있어도 떠나기를 거부한다
I'll handle the live broadcast issues
생방송 문제는 제가 처리하겠습니다
You must first find a way to help me find An Qiu
먼저 내가 An Qiu를 찾는 데 도움을 줄 방법을 찾아야 합니다.
Tomorrow evening
내일 저녁
I will reveal all the truth
모든 진실을 밝히겠습니다
Is it right to obviously abuse your power?
명백히 권력을 남용하는 것이 옳은 일인가요?
correct
옳은
Is it right to hide the truth?
진실을 숨기는 것이 옳은가?
It's the same as murder, isn't it?
살인과 똑같지 않나요?
correct
옳은
Minister Wan is here. Minister Wan is here.
완 장관이 왔어요 완 장관이 왔어요
Minister Wan, Minister Wan
완 장관, 완 장관
what do you think?
어떻게 생각하나요?
A case-handling officer abused his power
사건 처리 담당관이 직권을 남용했다
Things that hurt robots
로봇에게 상처를 주는 것들
1. The so-called assault incident
1. 이른바 폭행 사건
This did not happen in Mingmu
민무에서는 이런 일이 일어나지 않았습니다
We will contact Mingmo headquarters
밍모 본사에 연락드리겠습니다
Investigation into this incident
이번 사건에 대한 조사
Minister Wan
완 장관
mentioned in the video
영상에서 언급한
Robots with sparkling eyes watching you search
당신의 검색을 지켜보는 반짝이는 눈을 가진 로봇
conduct harsh experiments
가혹한 실험을 하다
Can you prove this?
이것을 증명할 수 있나요?
Dianyan tortures the robot from top to bottom
Dianyan은 로봇을 위에서 아래로 고문합니다.
i repeat
다시 한번 말한다
Bright eyes will never allow abuse to exist
밝은 눈은 학대를 결코 용납하지 않을 것입니다
The sister of the robot who was killed in the movie
영화에서 살해된 로봇의 여동생
He's the bright-eyed detective
그 사람은 눈이 밝은 탐정이에요
What is Ming's major?
밍이 전공이 뭐예요?
This is actually an internal mistake on our part.
이는 실제로 당사 내부의 실수입니다.
Minister Wan’s thoughts during this live broadcast
이번 생방송 중 완 장관의 생각
What do you want to respond to?
당신은 무엇에 응답하고 싶습니까?
I remind everyone
나는 모두에게 상기시킨다
Who planned this live broadcast?
누가 이 생방송을 계획했나요?
He is an android serial killer.
그는 안드로이드 연쇄 살인범입니다.
police arrested him
경찰이 그를 체포했다
I also hope that the general public
일반인들도 그랬으면 좋겠다
Do we really want to do this?
우리는 정말로 이것을 하고 싶은가?
Just do this
그냥 이렇게 하세요
Only in this way can everyone
그래야만 누구나 할 수 있다.
Get to know Mingmo’s true face
밍모의 진짜 얼굴을 알아보세요
dismantle them completely
완전히 해체해라
Will he come?
그 사람이 올까요?
He will definitely come
그 사람은 꼭 올 거야
Wanbo asked me to come over and help temporarily.
완보는 나에게 임시로 와서 도와달라고 부탁했다.
It’s not you who enters samadhi
삼매에 들어가는 것은 당신이 아니다
Don't you think it's strange?
이상하다고 생각하지 않나요?
Yin Tianhong’s goal has always been to kill the androids
Yin Tianhong의 목표는 항상 안드로이드를 죽이는 것이었습니다.
But not only did he not kill Anqiu,
그러나 그는 안추(Anqiu)를 죽이지 않았을 뿐만 아니라,
and set a trap for her
그리고 그녀를 위해 덫을 놓아
What is his goal?
그의 목표는 무엇입니까?
Kill more androids?
더 많은 안드로이드를 죽이시겠습니까?
And then there's his initial obsession
그리고 그의 초기 집착이 있습니다.
Is he just killing robots?
그는 단지 로봇을 죽이는 것입니까?
Why do employers buy cyborgs?
고용주가 사이보그를 구매하는 이유는 무엇입니까?
This led to his initial obsession with killing robots
이것은 로봇을 죽이는 것에 대한 그의 초기 집착으로 이어졌습니다.
Why is it impossible?
왜 불가능합니까?
Some owners are afraid to do it themselves
일부 소유자는 스스로 수행하는 것을 두려워합니다.
So buy a robot
그러니 로봇을 사세요
Just to experience the fun of killing
그냥 살인의 재미를 경험하기 위해
Even though his original obsession was killing robots
그의 원래 집착은 로봇을 죽이는 것이었지만
Also requires a switch to start
또한 시작하려면 스위치가 필요합니다.
Qingnu lied to you
칭누가 당신에게 거짓말을 했어요
Just like Luo Su lied to me back then
그때 Luo Su가 나에게 거짓말을 한 것처럼
Your brother died mysteriously
네 동생이 의문의 죽음을 맞이했어
Someone must want to help him take revenge
누군가는 그의 복수를 돕고 싶어 하는 게 틀림없어
If this is the case
만일이 경우라면
Sister Gu
구자매
The last survey you conducted contains results.
귀하가 실시한 마지막 설문조사에는 결과가 포함되어 있습니다.
This is Lao Qin
라오진입니다
It turns out that he is a security guard at Dreamland Club.
알고 보니 그는 드림랜드 클럽의 경비원이었다.
A few months ago I suddenly started looking for a buyer.
몇 달 전 갑자기 구매자를 찾기 시작했습니다.
Want to sell your Dream Club?
드림 클럽을 판매하고 싶으신가요?
same period
같은 기간
Large sums of money began to be transferred into his account
그의 계좌로 거액의 돈이 이체되기 시작했다.
I also found the suspicious account from which the payment was made.
결제가 이루어진 의심스러운 계좌도 찾아냈습니다.
Why you?
왜 네가?
In broad daylight you panic
대낮에 당신은 당황합니다
Are you afraid of anything?
당신은 무엇을 두려워합니까?
If someone attacks you from behind
누군가 뒤에서 공격한다면
Are not you afraid?
두렵지 않나요?
Are you afraid of Lao Chen?
라오첸이 두렵나요?
What are you afraid of?
당신은 무엇을 두려워합니까?
At most it's just a small ditch
기껏해야 작은 도랑에 불과하다
walk around
주위를 걷다
That's it
그게 다야
Then who are you afraid of?
그럼 당신은 누구를 두려워합니까?
It's Losu
로수예요
Still Yin Tianhong
스틸인티안훙
You are the owner of Dream Club
당신은 드림클럽의 주인입니다
I do not know what you're talking about
나는 당신이 무슨 말을하는지 모르겠어요
six years ago
6년 전
you are in dream club
당신은 드림클럽에 있어요
Illegal operation of electronic entertainment projects
전자 엔터테인먼트 프로젝트의 불법 운영
After announcing the summons
소환 발표 후
Instead, they went underground
대신 그들은 지하로 갔다
Also looking for new robots
새로운 로봇도 찾고 있어요
I was seriously violated
심각하게 침해당했어요
Saiyuan City’s “Robot Prohibition Law”
사이위안시의 '로봇 금지법'
Who did you hear this from?
누구한테서 이런 말을 들었나요?
Is it Lao Chen?
라오첸인가?
This guy of his is a thief
그 사람은 도둑이야
You believe everything he says
당신은 그가 말하는 모든 것을 믿습니다
i don't trust anyone
난 누구도 믿지 않아
I only believe in evidence
나는 증거만 믿는다
We found the surveillance system in the basement of Lao Chen's house
라오첸의 집 지하에서 감시 시스템을 발견했습니다
It contains the records of many of your meetings.
여기에는 많은 회의 기록이 포함되어 있습니다.
Do you want to borrow Lao Chen's hand?
라오첸의 손을 빌릴래?
Club was sold secretly
클럽은 비밀리에 매각되었습니다
The account used to transfer money to Lao Qin is also in your name.
Lao Qin으로 송금하는 데 사용된 계좌도 귀하의 이름으로 되어 있습니다.
The witnesses and physical evidence are all there
증인과 물적 증거는 모두 거기에 있습니다
If you still don't tell the truth
아직도 진실을 말하지 않는다면
Let us discuss these issues elsewhere.
이 문제는 다른 곳에서 논의해 보겠습니다.
I just want to know the truth about Luosu's death
나는 단지 루오수의 죽음에 대한 진실을 알고 싶을 뿐입니다
Rossu was one of the club's first players
Rossu는 클럽의 첫 번째 선수 중 한 명이었습니다.
android receptionist
안드로이드 접수원
Later I got sick
나중에 병이 났어요
He is no longer fit to be a receptionist
그는 더 이상 접수원이 될 자격이 없습니다
Staying in the club will only scare away customers
클럽에 있으면 손님이 겁을 먹을 뿐
I couldn't help but kick her out hard
나는 그녀를 세게 쫓아낼 수밖에 없었다.
But Luo Su was unwilling to do this
그러나 Luo Su는 이것을 원하지 않았습니다.
She begged me many times to let her back.
그녀는 나에게 자신을 돌려보내달라고 여러 번 간청했습니다.
Boss, please let me come back
사장님, 저 좀 돌아가게 해주세요
you look like this now
너 지금 이렇게 생겼어
I'm no longer cut out to be a receptionist.
나는 더 이상 접수원이 되기에 적합하지 않습니다.
As long as I don't leave the club
내가 클럽을 떠나지 않는 한
i can do anything
나는 모든것을 할수있다
You can do anything you want, can your mind do it?
당신은 당신이 원하는 것은 무엇이든 할 수 있습니다. 당신의 마음은 그것을 할 수 있습니까?
clear
분명한
look at yourself
너 자신을 봐
look at what it looks like now
지금 어떻게 생겼는지 좀 봐
Even if you flush the toilet
화장실 물을 내리더라도
People are going to hate you, okay?
사람들이 당신을 미워할 거예요, 그렇죠?
president
대통령
I have other things to do
난 다른 할 일이 있어
I can help the club with other things
나는 다른 일로 클럽을 도울 수 있다
I can help the club recruit robots
나는 클럽이 로봇을 모집하는 것을 도울 수 있습니다
Work as a receptionist
접수원으로 일하다
at all costs
모든 수단을 동원하여
The club was seriously short of players at the time.
당시 클럽에는 선수가 심각하게 부족했습니다.
Seeing how pitiful she was, I agreed.
그녀가 얼마나 불쌍한지 보고 나는 동의했습니다.
She was the one who recruited Yin Tianhong.
그녀는 Yin Tianhong을 영입한 사람이었습니다.
The night Luo Su was murdered
뤄수가 살해된 날 밤
Why is she back at the club?
그녀는 왜 클럽에 돌아왔나요?
That day is her birthday
그 날이 그 사람 생일이야.
She also invited many people to the club
그녀는 또한 많은 사람들을 클럽에 초대했습니다.
But who would have thought
하지만 누가 생각이나 했겠는가
Birthday turned into death anniversary
생일이 사망 기념일로 바뀌었습니다.
Yin Tianhong is here too
Yin Tianhong도 여기에 있습니다
Why did Yin Tianhong say that?
Yin Tianhong이 그런 말을 한 이유는 무엇입니까?
Russell betrayed him
러셀은 그를 배신했다
I have already sent a message to Cheng Nuo
이미 Cheng Nuo에게 메시지를 보냈습니다.
about there
거기쯤
I have a question
질문이 있어요
What was your first obsession?
당신의 첫 번째 집착은 무엇이었나요?
I do not remember
기억이 안나요
Maybe they were experimenting on me
어쩌면 그들은 나를 실험하고 있었을지도 모릅니다
Caused?
원인?
Of course it's not important
물론 중요한 건 아니지
Anyway, I'm just a nobody
어쨌든 난 아무 것도 아닌 사람이야
those who don't care about them
그들에게 관심이 없는 사람들
But until I met Luo Su
하지만 Luo Su를 만나기 전까지는
I understand your pain
나는 당신의 고통을 이해합니다
why not?
왜 안 돼?
look at me
날 봐
love this experience
이 경험을 사랑 해요
after tonight
오늘 밤 이후
there will be an end
끝이 있을 것이다
after everything is over
모든 것이 끝난 후에
let's get out of here
여기서 나가자
What's wrong
뭐가 문제 야
What has been lost?
무엇이 사라졌나요?
roll
롤
Now that it's solved
이제 해결되었으니
can you tell me then
그럼 나한테 말해줄래?
What is your purpose in doing all this?
이 모든 일을 하는 목적은 무엇입니까?
What are you so worried about?
뭘 그렇게 걱정해요?
just started
막 시작된
I think everyone is familiar with the face behind me
내 뒤의 얼굴은 모두가 익숙한 것 같아
It should be very familiar.
매우 익숙할 것입니다.
That's right, it was the one before
맞아요 예전에 그랬어요
Admit that you are taking advantage of your position
자신의 지위를 이용하고 있음을 인정하십시오.
The bright-eyed detective who persecutes androids at will
안드로이드를 마음대로 박해하는 밝은 눈의 탐정
Cheng Nu
쳉 누
Apparently you killed more androids
분명히 당신은 더 많은 안드로이드를 죽였습니다
Who are you to judge me?
네가 뭔데 나를 판단 해?
I admit
나는 인정한다
Do you admit it?
인정하시나요?
Or is it someone else's fault again?
아니면 또 다른 사람의 잘못인가요?
That was not what I meant
내 말은 그런 뜻이 아니었어
Why people?
왜 사람들이?
always blame others
항상 남을 탓한다
To cover up one's mistakes
자신의 실수를 덮기 위해
messenger of justice
정의의 메신저
Don’t you all need to think about it for yourself?
다들 스스로 생각해 볼 필요가 있지 않나요?
take a look at this
이것 좀 봐
This is the question Qingnv asked
Qingnv가 질문한 내용입니다.
The live broadcast should be here
생방송은 여기서 해야지
He notified the police and left immediately
경찰에 신고하고 바로 떠났다.
After a few years, I realized something
몇년이 지나서야 깨달은 게 있어요
Instead of killing with a knife
칼로 죽이는 것보다
verbal violence
언어폭력
and emotional abuse
그리고 정서적 학대
He is the one who really pushes people into the abyss.
그는 정말로 사람들을 심연으로 밀어넣는 사람입니다.
You should know that your mother suffered from depression before she was alive, right?
어머니가 생전에 우울증을 앓으셨다는 사실을 알아야겠죠?
I hear you, son, don't know anything about it
들었어, 아들아, 그것에 대해 아무것도 몰라
you before death
당신은 죽기 전에
he fought a good fight
그는 잘 싸웠다
Cut off the relationship between mother and child
엄마와 아이의 관계를 끊어라
He told her to find a robot for a son
그는 그녀에게 아들을 위한 로봇을 찾아보라고 말했습니다
So according to your logic
그러니 당신의 논리에 따르면
Your mother fell to death that night
네 어머니는 그날 밤에 돌아가셨어
It's everyone's fault
모두의 잘못이야
With you is a son who doesn't care about his mother.
당신과 함께 어머니를 신경 쓰지 않는 아들이 있습니다.
Not important at all, right?
전혀 중요하지 않죠?
damn it
젠장
I also have a responsibility
나에게도 책임이 있다
Advanced
고급의
I admit
나는 인정한다
but
하지만
Now that I admit it
이제 인정하니까
Are there any penalties?
처벌이 있나요?
I'm here today
나는 오늘 여기에 있다
Just to atone
단지 속죄하기 위해
I am willing to atone for Anyang's death
나는 안양의 죽음을 속죄할 용의가 있다
To atone for your sins and make you a guinea pig
당신의 죄를 속죄하고 당신을 실험용 돼지로 만들기 위해
chew
씹다
you can kill me
당신은 나를 죽일 수 있습니다
if you do
당신이 그렇게한다면
Let you make your own words
자신만의 말을 만들어 보자
chew
씹다
You don't just avenge your brother
넌 형에게 복수만 하는 게 아니야
At the same time, all robots should also be informed
동시에 모든 로봇에게도 정보가 제공되어야 합니다.
We can also break through our initial obsessions
우리는 또한 초기 집착을 깨뜨릴 수도 있습니다
You can also live for yourself
당신도 스스로 살아갈 수 있다